[Music]
Hey, what's up guys and gals? This is
for a review for the corrupts moon
rocks.
Um, so they come in this little thing
here.
Boom.
Um, I got pictures that I'll put in
right now.
Um, so that's what they look like up
close. One of these looks up like up
close.
Um,
all I got to say is, okay, at first I
was skeptical because I just kind of
thought it was going to be
um kind of covered up mediocre type
stuff. But it's definitely one of those
things for me cuz having a tolerance is
that it creeps.
Like um at first I was like, "Oh man."
And then all of a sudden I was like, "Oh
man."
So, um, these things are a little bit on
the expensive route because you probably
you're going through a co-op. I doubt
that the moon rocks they charge that
much for them um through the actual
through them themselves, but through my
co-op it was like 30 bucks or a gram.
So,
honestly, here in California, a lot of
people pay $20 a gram. And you know,
there's a lot of people go, "Oh, no, I
don't. No, I don't." [\h__\h] Because I
mean, it's like I'll give you an
example. It's like ice cream. Like,
yeah, you can get you can go to any
store and get ice cream, but you have to
go to like BaskinRobins to get banana
super fudged triple chocolate nut. So,
you can't get that anywhere else. So,
you have to go to that ice cream store.
even though you could readily buy it at
the you could buy ice cream itself at
the grocery store for just a couple
bucks. So that's kind of the same thing
with this is you know you could pay the
30 bucks and you're going to have a good
time.
Um
but I understand that it's this is like
you know I talk a lot about the
medicinal part of it but this is a party
favor. Like this is like to have fun.
Like I definitely we smoked some of this
and like you know we had fun. We watched
some movies and stuff and it was pretty
good. It was relaxed and then you know
it's one thing I like to preach about
when I people have anxiety. The only
thing I don't like is they don't tell
you what the CO2 oil is or what the the
actual keef is, which I kind of wish
that they would just just because people
some people will react with anxiety to
sativas like different and this is
pretty strong stuff especially I got
tolerance but I am having you know I'm
having a good time as they would say and
um
so anyways definitely if you have the
extra money to try it out at these would
be fun. Um,
so anyways, I that's my review and I can
tell you right now that um
I'm not going to be able to finish the
rest of that.
Not tonight.
But anyways, love piece of chicken
grease.
[Music]